readanddigest.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy – Read and Digest

Privacy Policy

* * *

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which ReadandDigest.com collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of the http://readanddigest.com website. This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by ReadAndDigest.com.

**Personal identification information**

We collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users register on the site, subscribe to the newsletter, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**General information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**Web browser cookies**

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**How we use collected information**

ReadandDigest.com may collect and use personal information of users for the following purposes:

  * **To improve our Site** – We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
  * **To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature** – To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password and data stored on our Site.

**Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

**Third party websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

**Advertising**

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you.

**The DoubleClick cookie**

  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website.
  * Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting the [ads preference manager](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/).

**Changes to this privacy policy**

ReadandDigest.com has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please send an email to contact@readanddigest.com. Detailed contact information can be found [here](http://readanddigest.com/contact-us/)

**Disclaimer**

All the content published is sole copyright of ReadandDigest.com, excluding materials such as images and videos which have written information about their original owner/source that permitted to use the same under the appropriate licensing terms. If anyone is referencing the content published, reference should be cited. The content cannot be used for any commercial purposes without any prior permission from ReadandDigest.com team.

By entering this site, you declare and affirm under the penalties of perjury that you are not a minor nor in the company of a minor and that accessing this site is not unlawful in your local area. You are entering this site of your own free volition and the owner of it accepts no responsibility for any individual’s experience within.

Information provided here is general in nature and is not intended to be a substitute for professional advice. For any medical condition, you must not rely on the information on this website as an alternative to medical advice from your doctor or other professional healthcare provider. While we try to provide accurate information, we make no claims, promises, or guarantees about the accuracy or completeness of the same.

User agrees that he or she will hold ReadandDigest.com harmless from all claims that may arise or result from any link to or content found on this domain. Furthermore, the user agrees that ReadandDigest.com cannot be held responsible for any damage, claims or any mishaps that may happen to occur from any link leading outside this site.

This document was last updated on August 10, 2012
